[airplane whooshing]
[upbeat rock music]
♪ All the small things ♪
♪ True care, truth brings ♪
♪ I'll take one lift ♪
♪ Your ride, best trip ♪
♪ Always I know ♪
♪ You'll be at my show ♪
♪ Watching, waiting ♪
♪ Commiserating ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ I will not go ♪
♪ Turn the lights off ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na,
na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Late night, come home ♪
♪ Work sucks, I know ♪
♪ She left me roses
by the stairs ♪
♪ Surprises let me
know she cares ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ I will not go ♪
♪ Turn the lights off ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na,
na-na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ I will not go ♪
♪ Turn the lights off ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ Keep your lips still ♪
♪ I'll be your thrill ♪
♪ The night will go on ♪
♪ My little windmill ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ I will not go ♪
♪ Turn the lights off ♪
♪ Carry me home ♪
♪ Keep your lips still ♪
♪ I'll be your thrill ♪
♪ The night will go on,
the night will go on ♪
♪ My little windmill ♪
♪♪♪